-你的咖啡  -谢谢
-Here you go. -Thank you.
是这样  瑞秋  我在想
"Say, Rachel...I was wondering
有空要不要一起去看电影
if you'd like go to a movie with me sometime...
以情侣的身份
as my lover."
太明显了
Too out there.
或者我们改天一起去吃饭
"Maybe you'd just like to get something to eat with me sometime...
以情侣的身份
as my lover."
-嗨  -嗨  走吧  买东西去
- Hi. - Hi. All right, let's go shopping.
走之前  我有话要说
Before we go, you know, there's something I need to say...
好吧  你说
Oh, OK.
我很喜欢你
I've kind of had this crush on you.
但以前你跟罗斯在一起  我就没有表白
But, since you were with Ross, I didn't do anything about it.
但既然你们分手了  我真的想约你出去
But, now that you're not, I'd really like to ask you out sometime.
所以  我现在就是在...约你
So that's what I'm doing... now.
我掉了一个杯子
I dropped a cup.
正因如此  几年内
You know, that's why within a few years,
语音识别系统将成为电脑的基本配置
voice recognition gonna be pretty much standard on any computer.
你可以说"去洗车"  "去打扫房间"
You know, so you could be, like, "Wash my car." "Clean my room."
电脑办不到这些
It's not gonna be able to do any of those things,
但是听得懂
but it'll understand what you're saying.
-好棒哦  -是啊
- Oh, this was so great. - Yeah, it was.
就这样吧
All right, then.
再见
Bye.
你们好啊  来串门的人
Hello, people who do not live here.
我给你们备用钥匙是有急事用的
I gave you a key for emergencies.
我们没有玉米片了
We were out of Doritos.
跟百万富翁的约会如何
Hey, how'd the date go with Mr. Millionaire?
骄傲玩具公司全新推出"百万富翁先生"
"Mr. Millionaire. New, from Snooty Playthings.
三姨太单独发售
Third wife sold separately."
他很棒  我们在一起很开心
He's great. I mean we have such a good time together.
他风趣又体贴
He's so funny and so sweet.
而我对他没半点兴趣
And I'm not attracted to him at all!
-还没兴趣吗  -没有
- Still? - No!
我快疯了
It's driving me crazy.
他各方面都很完美
In every other way, he's like the perfect guy.
他什么都不缺  他真的什么都有
He has everything. Plus, he actually has everything.
真人大小的《星球大战》帝国冲锋队模型呢
Life-sized Imperial StormTroopers from Sharper Image?
两套
Two.
乔伊和我可以穿起来对打吗
Can Joey and I put them on and fight?
老妈  老爸  我是超级坏小子
Oh, Mommy! Oh, Daddy! I am a big old baddy!
看来他一定接到那个舞台剧了
I guess he must've gotten the part in that play.
或者葛洛丽亚·伊斯特芬唱得对(歌手)
Either that, or Gloria Estefan was right.
人们迟早会随着这旋律起舞
Eventually, the rhythm is going to get you.
-乔伊  你好吗  -很好
- Joe, how's it going? - Good.
-你好  -你好
- Hey. - Hi.
这么说你演爱德莉安是吗
So you're playing Adrianne?
对  你是那些智障表亲中的一个吗
Yes. Are you one of the retarded cousins?
不是  我演你的丈夫维克多
No. I'm playing your husband, Victor.
我是乔伊.崔比安尼
I'm Joey Tribbiani.
很高兴认识你  我叫凯特.米勒
Hi. Nice to meet you. Kate Miller.
这个剧本很棒吧
So the play's pretty great, huh?
是啊  我好喜欢珍妮佛·班贝利的作品
Oh, yeah. I love Jennifer Banberry's work.
她尤其擅长
She's so brilliant incisive when it comes to
精确解构美国中产阶级的心态
deconstructing the psyche of the American middle class.
少说没用的  总之她特厉害
Oh, forget about it. She rocks!
我在哪里见过你
Where do I know you from?
德雷克·拉莫瑞医生
Dr. Drake Ramoray?
《我们的日子》
Days of our Lives?
《少年风尚》票选为
Voted most datable
最想与其约会的神经外科医生
neurosurgeon by Teen Beat?
不是那个
No, that's not it.
原来你是肥皂剧演员
So you're a soap actor.
能演出舞台剧  你一定很兴奋吧
This must be exciting for you, being in a real play.
我也演过舞台剧  我是专业演员
Hey, I've done plays before. I'm a serious actor.
那个电视购物广告
That infomercial!
牛奶盒专用倒出器那个
For the milk-carton-spout thing!
你是那个不会倒牛奶的人
You're the guy who doesn't know how to pour milk!
我其实会倒牛奶  但我把你骗了
I actually can pour milk. But I got you believing that I couldn't.
这就是演技
Now, see, that's acting.
最后你还被饼干噎到了
Right. At the end, you choked on a cookie.
那是真的
Yeah, that was real.
-真不敢相信马克居然约你出去  -是啊
-I cannot believe Mark asked you out. -I know.
那你要怎么回答
So what are you gonna tell him?
我跟他说我会考虑  但是我会拒绝
Well, I told him I would think about it, but I'm gonna tell him no.
我想现在我会拒绝任何人
I think I'd say no to anybody right now.
好奇怪  这样一个
But it was so strange. I mean, I 'm standing there with this
迷人  英俊的男人约我出去
charming, cute guy who's asking me to go out with him...
而且我也可以去  但我却有罪恶感
which I'm allowed to do and I felt guilty,
仿佛那样是背叛罗斯似的
You know like I'd be cheating on Ross or something.
也许这代表  你还没对罗斯忘情
Wow. So, okay, maybe that means that you're not over Ross yet
而且还有恋父情结
and you have issues with your father.
我没有恋父情结
I don't have issues with my father.
那可能只是罗斯的问题了
Okay. So it's probably just the Ross thing then.
我恨这个女人  我恨她
I hate this woman! I hate her!
她在剧组里到处宣扬购物广告的事
She told everyone in the company about that infomercial...
现在大家都跑来找我开饮料
and now they all keep asking me to open their drinks!
每次我打不开  他们就都
And whenever I can't do it, they're all, like,
都笑我
like laughing at me!
-你们好  -嘿
- Hello. - Hey.
瑞秋打电话来
So Rachel called.
说想见我
Wants to see me.
我待会就要过去
Going over in a minute.
你觉得她有什么事
What do you think she wants?
也许她茅塞顿开
Maybe the crazy fog has lifted...
发现没有我的人生
and she realizes that life without me...
是黑白的
are sucks.
有可能  你很可爱
It's possible. You are very lovable.
要是我跟你分手  也会想你的
I'd miss you if I broke up with you.
我只是想表达支持
Just trying to be supportive.
请以男人的方式来表达
Be supportive like a guy.
要是我跟你分手  也会想念你
If I broke up with you, I'd miss you.
你找我
You wanted to see me?
是的
Yeah.
这一盒是你的东西
Here's a box of your stuff.
什么
what?
就是几顶帽子  一件衣服  几张唱片
It's just like hats and a shirt and CD's.
一些你留在这里的东西
Just sort of stuff that you've left here.
你想干什么  这是想伤害我还是怎样
What are you doing? Are you trying to hurt me or something?
不是
No.
罗斯
Ross.
只是...
It just seems that, you know,
我们该放下过去了  你不同意吗
it's time we move on. I mean, don't you think?
-同意啊  -那就好
- Yes. - Yeah.
我非常同意
Yes, I do. I really do.
这是我送你的礼物
This was a gift.
罗斯  那是博物馆礼品店的赠品
Ross. You got that for free from the museum gift shop.
一样是礼物  我是从"礼品店"拿到的
It's still a gift. I got it from the "gift" shop.
好  杯子给我  我留着就是了
Okay! All right! Give me the mug! I'll keep the mug!
不  不必假好心
No, you know, don't do me any favors.
我想问  我的其它东西呢
In fact...where's the rest of my stuff?
比如说...
Like my....
这本书是我的
This book is mine!
你当成睡衣穿的T恤呢  我要拿回来
And that T-shirt you sleep in? I'd like that back too.
我就要
Yes, I do.
你明知我很喜欢那件衣服
You know how much I love that T-shirt.
你根本没穿过
You never even wear that T-shirt.
我是在帮你往前走
I'm just trying to help you "move on."
你真小气
Oh, you are a petty man.
-非常  非常小气...  -小气...
- You are a petty, petty...  - Petty...
-小心眼...  -小心眼...
- small... - small...
你这么做就是为了泄愤
You are so just doing this out of spite.
才不是  我会一直穿着  我爱这件衣服
No no no, I'm gonna wear this all the time! I love this shirt!
你15岁后就没穿过了
You haven't worn that T-shirt since you were 15!
根本塞不下
It doesn't even fit you anymore!
-是吗  是吗  -就是  就是
- Oh, yeah-yeah... - Yeah-yeah...
好吧  好吧
OK, OK.
不好意思  我要把其它东西拿走了
If you don't mind, I'm gonna take the rest of my stuff...
然后穿着我最爱的衣服  去放松一下
and "relax"...in my favorite shirt.
祝你今晚愉快
You have a pleasant evening.
这么说  你是亿万富翁
So you're, like, a zillionaire.
却跟我们差不多大  差不多大啊
And you're our age. You're our age.
知道吗  你应该买下一个州
You know what? You should buy a state...
然后用你的名字给它命名
and then just name it after yourself.
比如"彼特达科他州"
Like, "Pete Dakota"?
或是"密西西彼特州"
Or "Mississi-Pete."
我想到了  "彼芝加哥"
I got it: "Pete Chicago."
芝加哥不是州  乔伊
That's not a state, Joe.
那"密西西彼特"就是吗
Oh, and "Mississi-Pete" is?
我该走了  改天见
I gotta go. So I'll see you guys later.
-好的  -你居然跟我们差不多大
-Ok. - You're our age.
-那我们明天照旧  -好的
- So are we on for tomorrow? - Absolutely.
快走吧
Now, get out of here, you!
我快要没地方可以摸了
Okay, I'm running out of places I can touch him.
我是有什么毛病吗
Is something wrong with me?
为何我总是喜欢与之没有未来的人
Why am I only attracted to guys with there's no future?
不是太老  就是太小
Either they're too old, or they're too young.
而彼特这么喜欢我
And there's Pete, who's crazy about me......
又这么完美  我却一点感觉也没有
and he's absolutely perfect, and there's zip going on!
真的  你们觉得我是不是有什么毛病
Seriously, does it sound like something's wrong with me?
好像是有点
Yeah, kind of.
开心  我应该感到开心吗  维克
Happy? Is that what I'm supposed to be, Vic?
开心
Happy?
不如你来告诉我你该有什么感觉
Why don't you tell me what you're supposed to be?
因为我实在搞不懂
Because I sure as hell can't figure it out!
我们的交谈没有感情
I talk to you, and nothing!
你看着我的眼神没有感情
You look at me, and it's nothing!
一点都没有
Nothing.
有意思
Tasty.
我开始觉得你们有渊源了  很好
I'm really starting to feel like you guys have a history. It's nice.
-我对这场戏有个疑问  -怎样
- I have a question about this scene. - Yes?
我不理解爱德莉安为什么会喜欢维克多
I don't understand why Adrianne's attracted to Victor.
抽丝剥茧
Peel the onion.
首先  他很帅
First of all, he's good-looking.
我的角色需要更好的理由
I think my character needs a little bit more of a reason than that.
我来告诉你个理由  因为剧本这么写的
Hey, how about this one? It says so in the script!
我也不明白我的角色为什么喜欢你
You know I don't know why my character likes you either.
剧本上说你是个贱人
I mean, it says in the script here that you're a bitch.
-剧本上没写  -我这本有
- It doesn't say that in the script. - It does in mine.
我吹干  上发胶  还是一样
I can blow-dry it, I can put gel on it. It doesn't matter.
头顶上还是有一撮
I still wind up with this little...
梳不平的头发  烦死人了
cowlick-y thing on the middle part of my head. It's so annoying.
-你看了烦不烦  -你比较烦
- Does it bug you? - You bug me.
你会不会刚好没看到
Is there any chance you didn't see that?
罗斯  别再看了
Ross, you gotta stop, okay?
你不能在猫眼那儿瞄上三小时
You can't just stare through the peephole for three hours.
你会得偷窥眼的
You're gonna get peep-eye.
我就知道  我就知道她喜欢他
I knew it. I knew it. I always knew she liked him.
她一直否认  结果呢
She'd say no,but here we are.
我们才刚分手  她就变心了
We just broke up, first thing she does!
-你们可不是"才刚"分手  -才三个星期
- You didn't "just break up." - It's been, like, three weeks!
你跟她分手后不到三小时就跟别人上床了
You slept with somebody three hours after you thought you broke up.
连子弹出膛都没这么快
I mean, bullets have left guns slower.
他们回来了  他们
Here they come! Here they...
要是她跟他吻别  我发誓我会自杀的
If she kisses him good night, I'm gonna kill myself. I swear.
我看不下去了
I can't watch.
约会该结束了  该结束了
Come on. Date over! Date over!
-没事  她要进去了  -好的
- Here we go. She's going in. - Okay.
她要进去了
She's going in.
等等  他也要进去了
Wait! He's going in!
他进去了  门关了
He's going in!The door's closed!
门关着我什么都看不到
I can't see anything with the door closed!
门的发明者可以安息了
And the inventor of the door rests happily in his grave.
我得想个办法  我得阻止他们
I have to do something. I have to stop it!
-阻止什么  -我不知道
- Stop what? - I don't know.
但我觉得我到他们屋里就想明白了
But I ah, I have the feeling that my being there will do it.
我要过去借东西  果汁  我要喝果汁
I'll go over and I will borrow something! Juice! I need juice!
不行
No! You can't!
一定要阻止他们
They must be stopped!
我是你的朋友  我不会让你这么做的
I am your friend and I am not gonna let you do this!
你还真强壮
You are surprisingly strong!
我要喝果汁  人都要喝果汁
I need juice! People need juice!
-听着  伙计  -人都要喝果汁
- Look, man... - People need juice!
-听我说  -果汁  我要喝...
- Listen to me! - Juice! I need...
她放下过去了
She's moving on. Okay?
就算不是他也会有别人
If it's not this guy, it's gonna be somebody else.
除非你打算租下这个猫眼
And unless you're thinking about subletting my peephole...
否则你就得
you're gonna have to get used to
面对分手的事实
the fact that the relationship is over!
好吗  兄弟  结束了
Okay, man? It's over.
好吧
Yeah. Okay.
那就好
Okay.
我真的很想她
It's just I miss her so much.
我知道
I know.
咖啡杯底为什么都有编号
Why do your coffee mugs have numbers on the bottom?
这样莫妮卡才方便追踪
Oh, that's so Monica can keep track.
要是少了一个
That way if one of them's missing,
她就可以说  "27号杯呢"
she can be like, "Where's number 27?"
-你知道吗  -不知道  也不想知道
- You know what?- No, and I don't think I'm gonna want to.
-我办不到  -我就是不想知道这件事
- I can't do this. - Yeah, yeah. That's what I didn't want to know.
马克  我的出发点是错的
Oh, Mark, I'm just doing this for the wrong reasons, you know?
我只是想报复罗斯
I'm just doing it to get back at Ross.
对不起  这样对你不公平
I'm sorry. It's not very fair to you.
去他的公平
Fair, shmair. You know?
你想报复罗斯  尽管找我
Look, you wanna get back at Ross, I am here for you.
真的  要我说
Really. No, no. I say
我们就在这张沙发上报复他吧
I say we get back at him right here on this couch. Right here!
天哪
Oh, my God.
很抱歉
I'm sorry about this.
没关系
That's okay.
-你确定  -是的
- You sure? - Yeah.
我可以回去自己报复他
I can just go home and get back at him by myself.
...它将成为21世纪的青霉素
...and should become the penicillin of the 21st century.
所以今天  本院将迈出领导改革的
And so today, this hospital is about to take major steps...
关键一步
toward leading that revolution.
问你一件事
Can I ask you something?
目前是什么状况
Where are we?
有这么多医生和护士在场
Well, with all these doctors and nurses...
应该是侏儒马术表演
I'm gonna say, "Midget Rodeo."
跟我说实话
Just tell me the truth.
好吧
OK.
我应该没有告诉你  但是
You know, I don't think I told you this but...
我刚结束一段很认真的感情
I just recently got out of a really serious relationship.
那不是都一年前的事了吗
Oh, right. Wasn't that a year ago?
原来我说过了
So I did tell you.
其实不是这个原因
Okay, you know? That's not really the thing.
原因是目前
The thing is that right now
我只想把注意力放在自己身上
I'm just in a place in my life where I just need to focus on me.
-你懂吗  -我懂
- Do you know what I mean? - Oh, I know what are you mean.
我也想对你有兴趣
I so want to be attracted to you.
但是你没有  好了  没事
But you're not. Okay. Good.
对不起
I'm sorry.
知道吗  不必抱歉
You know what, don't be, it's not,
不必抱歉  没有那么糟
don't be, because it's not so bad.
真的
It's not?
我又不是约翰·邦乔维(摇滚明星)
Yeah. I know I'm no Jon Bon Jovi.
或是对你有吸引力的人
Or someone you find attractive.
我只是觉得
I just think, you know...
你的感觉或许会变
that you might end up feeling differently.
你别误会  但是
I don't want this to come out wrong but...
以被拒绝的人来说
you seem awfully confident for a guy
你还真有自信
I just told I wasn't attracted to.
傻得很可爱吧
Stupidly charming, isn't it?
要不要去吃饭
Listen, let's... You wanna get something to eat?
这里太令人沮丧了
This place is kind of depressing.
我们欢迎幕后功臣
Now the man who made all of this possible,
彼特·贝克先生
Mr. Peter Becker.
等一下
One second.
一山不容二虎
I don't think this town is big enough for the both of us to relax in.
拔枪
Draw!
我什么也没做
I wasn't doing anything.
她又怎么了
What did she do now?
她不过在耶鲁大学读过戏剧系
Just because she went to Yale drama,
就自以为是有史以来最伟大的女演员
she thinks she's like the greatest actress...since sliced bread.
切片面包啊  她演的麦克白夫人是一绝
Ah, Sliced Bread. A wonderful Lady Macbeth.
老天  我恨她  我恨她成天
God. I hate her. I hate her with her
"我好有才华"
"Oh, I'm so talented"...
还有"我好漂亮"  "我好香"
and "Oh, I'm so pretty," and "Oh, I smell so good."
我看有某人动了心哦
I think somebody has a crush on somebody.
钱德勒  请专心讨论我的问题好吗
Chandler can we please try and stay focused on my problem here?
我就是说你  猪头
I'm talking about you, you big, big freak.
别说疯话
You're out of your mind!
这两天你开口闭口都是她
You've done nothing but talk about her for the last 48 hours.
要是你还是学生
If you were in school,
你早就在拉她的辫子  推倒她了
you'd be pulling her pigtails and pushing her down now.
是吗  那为什么我老是想着
Oh yeah? Then how come I keep thinking about her...
跟她在各种场景中嘿咻呢
in all these sexual scenarios and stuff?
开心  我应该感到开心吗  维克  开心
Happy? Is that what I'm supposed to be, Vic? Happy?
不如你来告诉我你该有什么感觉
Why don't you tell me what you're supposed to be, huh?
因为我实在搞不懂
Because I sure as hell can't figure it out.
我们的交谈没有感情
I talk to you, and it's nothing.
你看着我的眼神没有感情
You look at me, and nothing.
一点都没有
Nothing.
你们让我乐翻天了
You guys make me fly!
乐死了
High!
明天从这一幕开始继续排
Okay, we're gonna pick it up here, tomorrow.
-刚才实在是...  -好多了
- Well, that was.... - Better?
是的  毫无疑问
Yeah, it was definitely...
的确有进步
an improvement.
晚安
Good night.
-凯特  -嗯
- Kate. - Yeah?
你忘了穿鞋子
You forgot your shoes.
不穿鞋子恐怕不行  是不是
I'm probably gonna need those, huh?
听着
Hey, listen...
要不要跟我去喝杯咖啡
you feel like getting a cup of coffee?
凯特
Kate...
可以走了吗
you ready to go?
非常好  非常好
Very nice. Very nice.
那么
So...
-明天见  -好
- See you tomorrow? - Yeah. Sure.
-那好  -晚安
- Right. - Good night.
为什么没有叫"斯派德曼"的
Why isn't it "Spiderman"?
像是高德曼  西尔弗曼
Like Goldman, Silverman?
因为那不是他的姓
Because it's not his last name.
-不是吗  -他又不叫
- It isn't? - No, it's not, like...
菲尔·斯派德曼
Phil Spiderman.
他是个蜘蛛...侠
He's a Spider-man.
比如说
You know, like
像高德曼是姓氏  但是没有金人
Goldman is a last name. But there's no Gold Man.
好吧
Okay.
应该有金人的
There should be a Gold Man!
瑞秋
Hi, Rach.
-工作顺利吗  -不错
- How was work? - Oh, great.
只是我坐下的时候不小心摔到地上了
Although I did sit down where there wasn't a chair.
对了  罗斯拿了一盒你的东西来
By the way, Ross dropped by a box of your stuff.
意料之中的事
Oh. Well, I guess I had that one coming.
直接扔掉吧  还不是洗发水还有...
I'm just gonna throw it out. It's probably just shampoo and...
怎么了
Something wrong?
没  没事
No. Nothing.
那么  "金人"有什么超能力
So what kind of powers would "Gold Man" have?
他能把东西变成金子
Okay. Well, he would turn things to gold.
-已经是金子的东西呢  -那他就不用变了
- What about things that are already gold? - His work is done.
-来玩我的游戏吧  -好
- Okay. Let's play my game now. - Okay.
你这个胆小如鼠的懦夫
All right, you yellow-bellied, lily-livered...
拔枪
Draw!
太有趣了
Yey, it is fun.